const macgyverQuizData = [
    {
        QuizName: "Macgyver"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "1",
        Question: "Who is the actor who plays MacGyver?",
        Options: ["Bruce McGill", "Dana Elcar", "Richard Dean Anderson", "Michael Des Barres"],
        Answer: "Richard Dean Anderson"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "2",
        Question: "What is MacGyver's grandfathers's name?",
        Options: ["Harry Jackson", "Guy Roberts", "Jesse Colton", "Peter Thornton"],
        Answer: "Harry Jackson"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "3",
        Question: "Who is the voodoo priestess in MacGyver?",
        Options: ["Nikki Carpenter", "Lisa Woodman", "Penny Parker", "Mama Lorain"],
        Answer: "Mama Lorain"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "4",
        Question: "Who are the three Colton brothers?",
        Options: ["Frank, Jesse, Perry", "Billy, Frank, Jesse", "Tim, Billy, Irwin", "Jesse, Perry, Tim"],
        Answer: "Billy, Frank, Jesse"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "5",
        Question: "What is the name of the Colton family dog?",
        Options: ["Frog", "Dog", "Buddy", "Abe"],
        Answer: "Frog"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "6",
        Question: "Who was MacGyver's friend who died while trying to defuse a bomb at sea?",
        Options: ["Robert Sanborn", "Larry Whitecloud", "Charlie Robinson", "Darin Cooper"],
        Answer: "Charlie Robinson"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "7",
        Question: "What is the name of MacGyver's son?",
        Options: ["Tim Wexler", "Caspar Kasabian", "Henry Jones", "Sean Malloy"],
        Answer: "Sean Malloy"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "8",
        Question: "How many seasons did MacGyver have?",
        Options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        Answer: "7"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "9",
        Question: "How can you tell when Jack Dalton is 'stretching the truth'?",
        Options: ["He laughs", "He doesn't make eye contact", "His eye twitches", "He wrings his hands"],
        Answer: "His eye twitches"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "10",
        Question: "MacGyver works for two companies throughout the series. What is the second company?",
        Options: ["Spy Center Inc.", "Department of External Services", "Central Intelligence Agency", "Phoenix Foundation"],
        Answer: "Phoenix Foundation"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "11",
        Question: "Based on the previous question, which company did he first work at?",
        Options: ["Department of External Services", "Central Intelligence Agency", "Phoenix Foundation", "Spy Center Inc."],
        Answer: "Department of External Services"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "12",
        Question: "Where does MacGyver meet Penny Parker?",
        Options: ["Restaurant", "Airport", "Bank", "Grocery Store"],
        Answer: "Airport"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "13",
        Question: "Who is MacGyver's greatest foe?",
        Options: ["Matlock", "Brandenberg", "Malcolm", "Murdoc"],
        Answer: "Murdoc"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "14",
        Question: "What is MacGyver's favorite sport?",
        Options: ["Soccer", "Football", "Hockey", "Baseball"],
        Answer: "Hockey"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "15",
        Question: "Why didn't MacGyver like guns?",
        Options: ["They are too loud", "He never grew up around them", "Childhood incident", "He actually loved them"],
        Answer: "Childhood incident"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "16",
        Question: "In the episode 'Two Times Trouble,' Carla impersonates her twin sister. Who is this?",
        Options: ["Roxanne", "Judy", "Michelle", "Charity"],
        Answer: "Roxanne"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "17",
        Question: "Who runs the Challenger's club alongside his wife, Cynthia?",
        Options: ["Larry", "Booker", "Andrew", "Robert"],
        Answer: "Booker"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "18",
        Question: "What is the name of the restaurant that MacGyver helps Earl Dent get a job at?",
        Options: ["Los Polos Hermanos", "Mr. Cluck's Chicken Shack", "Cluckin' Bell", "Chicken Habit"],
        Answer: "Chicken Habit"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "19",
        Question: "Who tried teaching MacGyver a 'lesson in evil'?",
        Options: ["Murdoc", "Deborah", "Zito", "Nicolai Kossov"],
        Answer: "Zito"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "20",
        Question: "What is MacGyver's first name?",
        Options: ["Angus", "Harry", "Dexter", "Craig"],
        Answer: "Angus"
    }
]